Mommy.
‫أمي.‬
Don't let go of my hand, Mommy.
‫لا تفلتي يدي يا أمي.‬
Mommy!
‫أمي!‬
The man… He was a Czechoslovakian of German ancestry.
‫الرجل كان تشيكوسلوفاكيًا من أصل ألماني.‬
He was the eldest son of a family who remained in Bohemia
‫كان أكبر ابن في عائلة بقيت في "بوهيميا"‬
after World War Two.
‫بعد الحرب العالمية الثانية.‬
He was a soldier who graduated from a military academy.
‫كان جنديًا تخرّج في أكاديمية عسكرية.‬
He was a member of the elite who would lead his country to the future.
‫كان عضوًا من النخبة‬ ‫التي ستقود هذا البلد إلى المستقبل.‬
His name…
‫اسمه…‬
That does not matter.
‫ليس بأمر مهم.‬
The woman…
‫المرأة…‬
She was the only daughter of elementary school teachers in Moravia.
‫كانت الابنة الوحيدة لمدرسين في الابتدائية‬ ‫في "مورافيا".‬
She was a beautiful woman with blonde hair and blue eyes.
‫كانت جميلة وشقراء وزرقاء العينين.‬
She entered Brno University and majored in genetic engineering.
‫التحقت بجامعة "برنو"‬ ‫وتخصصت في الهندسة الوراثية.‬
Her professors said she was talented and had a bright future.
‫قال أساتذتها إنها كانت موهوبة‬ ‫وينتظرها مستقبل باهر.‬
Her name…
‫اسمها…‬
does not matter.
‫ليس له أهمية.‬
The two of them met at a cafe in Prague.
‫تقابلا في مقهى في "براغ".‬
It didn't take long before they fell in love.
‫وسرعان ما وقعا في غرام أحدهما الآخر.‬
Before long, the woman became pregnant.
‫وسرعان ما حملت المرأة.‬
Then the man told her…
‫من ثم أخبرها الرجل…‬
"I was assigned to do this."
‫"كُلّفت بفعل ذلك.‬
"Men and women have been chosen based on their race, intelligence,
‫اُختير رجال ونساء بناءً على أعراقهم وذكائهم،‬
physical features, and athletic ability to have children together."
‫ومعالم أجسادهم وقدراتهم البدنية،‬ ‫لينجبوا أطفالًا.‬
"It is an experiment being done with several dozen couples."
‫إنها تجربة تُجرى على عدة عشرات من الأزواج.‬
"We are one of those couples in this experiment."
‫نحن من أزواج هذه التجربة."‬
The man carried out his assignment according to the plan.
‫نفّذ الرجل مهمته وفقًا لما خُطط له.‬
He told her that he now had no intention of following it.
‫أخبرها بأنه ما عاد ينوي اتباعها.‬
Then he said…
‫ثم قال…‬
Let's run away!
‫لنهرب!‬
The two of them ran away.
‫وهربا.‬
The man declared that he wouldn't follow their plan.
‫صرّح الرجل بأنه لن يتّبع خطتهم.‬
But his actions were already figured into the plan.
‫لكن أفعاله كانت قد وُضعت في الحسبان.‬
The woman was confined in an unfamiliar room.
‫حُجزت المرأة في غرفة غير مألوفة.‬
Let me see him.
‫اسمحي لي برؤيته.‬
He's been given a new assignment.
‫كُلّف بمهمة جديدة.‬
She said,
‫قالت،‬
"Let me see him."
‫"اسمح لي برؤيته."‬
But she knew
‫لكنها كانت تعرف‬
that he was already no longer alive.
‫أنه ما عاد حيًا.‬
The children she carried developed normally.
‫نما طفلاها من حملت بهما على نحو طبيعي.‬
She was carrying twins.
‫كانا توأم.‬
Look this way.
‫انظري نحوي.‬
She began to realize…
‫بدأت تدرك‬
that this man who often visited…
‫أن الرجل الذي كان كثيرًا ما يزورها‬
and who sketched pictures of her…
‫وأخذ يرسم رسومات لها…‬
that this man was the one who had masterminded this experiment.
‫هو العقل المدبر لهذه التجربة.‬
I won't forgive this.
‫لن أعفو عمّا حدث.‬
I will never forgive you.
‫لن أعفو عنك أبدًا.‬
Even if I die,
‫حتى إن مت،‬
the children growing inside me,
‫فطفلاي اللذان في أحشائي،‬
I swear they will take vengeance on you.
‫سينتقمان منك وأقسم لك بذلك.‬
You say the most amusing things.
‫تتحدثين بكلام يسلّيني.‬
She came due and started going into labor.
‫حان وقت الولادة وبدأت تحيض.‬
She was moved to a different room to ease the labor pains.
‫انتقلت من غرفة إلى أخرى‬ ‫لتخفيف آلام المخاض.‬
That's when she took action.
‫عندئذ تصرّفت.‬
Though the air vent was only
‫مع أن فتحة التهوية‬
a couple dozen centimeters wide, she dragged her heavy body
‫كانت مساحتها تبلغ بضع سنتمترات،‬ ‫إلا أنها جرّت جسدها الثقيل‬
wracked by labor pains through it to escape.
‫وهي تتعذّب بآلام المخاض لتهرب.‬
She collapsed on the road a few dozen meters from the front gate.
‫سقطت على الطريق‬ ‫على بُعد بضعة أمتار من البوابة الأمامية.‬
Her water was already broken.
‫كان ماء الحيض قد نزل.‬
How beautiful.
‫ما أجملهما.‬
Such beautiful children.
‫ما أجملهما من طفلين.‬
So, these are the children that will lead the future of humanity.
‫هذان الطفلان إذًا‬ ‫هما من سيقودان مستقبل البشرية.‬
They're magnificent.
‫إنهما مذهلان.‬
I thought of names for them.
‫فكّرت في اسمين لهما.‬
Don't bother yourself with such pointless matters.
‫لا تشغلي بالك بأمور لا طائل منها.‬
I have thought of names for the babies.
‫فكّرت في اسمين لطفليّ.‬
You don't need to do that.
‫ما من ضرورة لذلك.‬
Give them names.
‫امنحهما اسمين.‬
Give those children names!
‫امنح الطفلين اسمين.‬
You must!
‫يجب أن تفعل هذا!‬
Forget it.
‫دعك من هذا.‬
They don't need names.
‫ليسا بحاجة إلى اسمين.‬
Franz Bonaparta…
‫"فرانس بونابارتا"…‬
That's right.
‫هذا صحيح.‬
Johan asked me where he is.
‫سألني "يوهان" عن مكانه.‬
Do you mean Bonaparta lives?
‫أتعني أن "بونابارتا" حيّ؟‬
"I won't forgive this."
‫"لن أعفو عمّا حدث.‬
"I will never forgive you."
‫لن أعفو عنك.‬
"Even if I die,
‫حتى إن مت،‬
the children growing inside me,
‫فطفلاي اللذان في أحشائي،‬
I swear they will take vengeance on you."
‫سينتقمان منك وأقسم لك بذلك."‬
Franz Bonaparta lives, doesn't he?
‫"فرانس بونابارتا" حيّ، أليس كذلك؟‬
Ask Johan.
‫اسألي "يوهان".‬
He is here.
‫أنه هنا.‬
You're one hell of a doctor.
‫يا لك من طبيب.‬
There's a hospital up ahead.
‫ثمة مستشفى أمامنا.‬
I'll take you there if you tell me where Johan is.
‫سآخذك إليها إن أخبرتني بمكان "يوهان".‬
If you don't go, you'll die from blood loss.
‫إن لم تذهب، فستنزف حتى الموت.‬
I… don't know what I don't know.
‫لا أعرف ما لا أعرفه.‬
Hurry up and tell us!
‫أخبرنا بسرعة!‬
You're one hell of a doctor.
‫يا لك من طبيب.‬
Not only did you shoot me,
‫لم تطلق عليّ النار فحسب،‬
you let me bleed like this then proceed to blackmail me.
‫بل تركتني أنزف ومن ثم تبتزني.‬
Where is Johan?
‫أين "يوهان"؟‬
You're one hell of a doctor.
‫يا لك من طبيب.‬
Hurry up and tell us! Now!
‫أخبرنا بسرعة! في الحال!‬
I don't know what I don't know.
‫لا أعرف ما لا أعرفه.‬
Eva.
‫"إيفا".‬
There's a payphone over there.
‫ثمة هاتف عام هناك.‬
Call the hospital and tell them that a man bleeding in this car.
‫اتصلي بالمستشفى وأخبريهم‬ ‫بأن ثمة رجل ينزف في هذه السيارة.‬
Are you insane?
‫هل فقدت عقلك؟‬
He's about to tell us--
‫يوشك على أن يخبرنا…‬
If we wait any longer, he could die.
‫إن انتظرنا أكثر، فقد يموت.‬
Hurry up and call.
‫اتصلي بهم بسرعة.‬
You've saved a life again.
‫أنقذت حياة أخرى.‬
You always end up doing this.
‫دائمًا ما تفعل هذا.‬
You can't kill anyone.
‫لا يمكنك قتل أحد.‬
He's been wanting to see you.
‫كان يريد رؤيتك.‬
So I'll tell you… where Johan is.
‫لذلك سأخبرك بمكان "يوهان".‬
Kenzo, an ambulance from the hospital will be here soon.
‫ستُرسل سيارة إسعاف من المستشفى‬ ‫بعد قليل يا "كينزو".‬
We need to get out of--
‫يجب أن نخرج…‬
Where's Kenzo?
‫أين "كينزو"؟‬
He left.
‫غادر.‬
He left a message for you.
‫ترك لك رسالة.‬
"I can't let you get any more involved than you already are."
‫"لا يمكنني أن أسمح بتورطك أكثر في ذلك.‬
"I ruined your life."
‫أنا دمّرت لك حياتك.‬
"I'm very sorry for that. I hope you find happiness."
‫أعتذر بشدة عن ذلك. أرجو أن تجدي السعادة."‬
Why are you crying?
‫لماذا تبكين؟‬
I can't understand it.
‫لا أستوعب ذلك.‬
It makes no sense to me at all.
‫لا أجد هذا منطقيًا على الإطلاق.‬
Johan.
‫"يوهان".‬
THREE FROGS
‫"(الثلاثة ضفادع)"‬
NAMELESS MONSTER
‫"(وحش بلا اسم)"‬
Welcome back.
‫عودًا حميدًا.‬
Fire!
‫حريق!‬
The Three Frogs is burning!
‫مبنى "الثلاثة ضفادع" يحترق.‬
Go on. Eat up.
‫هيا، تناولا الطعام.‬
It will get caught in your throat if you eat so quickly.
‫سيعلق الطعام في حلقيكما إن أكلتما بسرعة.‬
You must be awfully hungry.
‫لا بد أنكما تضوران جوعًا.‬
So, where are you two from?
‫من أين أنتما؟‬
What are your names?
‫ما اسماكما؟‬
They don't want to talk at all.
‫لا يريدان التحدّث مطلقًا.‬
That's okay. You can talk once you've eaten your fill.
‫لا بأس بذلك. يمكنكما التحدّث ما إن تشبعا.‬
Wait up!
‫انتظر!‬
-Wait for me! -Over here!
‫- انتظرني.‬ ‫- تعالي!‬
What will we do?
‫ماذا سنفعل؟‬
What do you mean?
‫ما قصدك؟‬
Don't you think those children have parents somewhere?
‫أتظن أن لهما والدين في مكان ما؟‬
Even if they do, they must have a reason for not going back.
‫حتى وإن كان الأمر كذلك،‬ ‫فلا بد من وجود سبب يمنعهما من الرجوع.‬
You and I…
‫أنا وأنت…‬
We always wanted children.
‫لطالما أردنا أن نُرزق بالأطفال.‬
That's true.
‫صحيح.‬
Why don't we adopt--
‫لم لا نتبناهما…‬
Don't be ridiculous!
‫كفاك سخافة!‬
I'm sorry for getting angry.
‫أعتذر عمّا أبديته من غضب.‬
We should call the police.
‫يجب أن نتصل بالشرطة.‬
What's wrong, little boy?
‫ما الخطب يا صبي؟‬
Look at these! Aren't they pretty flowers?
‫انظر إلى هذه! أليست أزهارًا جميلة؟‬
I'll give them to the old man and woman.
‫سأعطيها للمسنّ والمرأة العجوز.‬
You don't need to.
‫لا داعي لذلك.‬
Why?
‫لماذا؟‬
Remember what I said?
‫أنسيت ما قلته؟‬
I've got a good plan.
‫لديّ خطة مُحكمة.‬
Come on.
‫هيا.‬
Oh darn you!
‫سحقًا لك!‬
Wait up!
‫انتظر!‬
Wait! Come on!
‫مهلًا! تعال!‬
At last, we meet.
‫تقابلنا أخيرًا.‬
When I escaped from the Red Rose Mansion
‫عندما هربت من قصر "الوردة الحمراء"‬
and arrived at our place at the Three Frogs…
‫ووصلت إلى مسكننا في مبنى "الثلاثة ضفادع"…‬
you welcomed me back.
‫رحّبت بعودتي.‬
So this time it's my turn to say it to you.
‫ولذلك حان دوري للترحيب بك.‬
Welcome back.
‫عودًا حميدًا.‬
A lot of time has passed…
‫مضى وقت طويل‬
since I came to get you in Heidelberg on your 20th birthday.
‫على ذهابي لإحضارك في "هايدلبرغ"‬ ‫في عيد مولدك الـ20.‬
"Came to get me"?
‫"لإحضاري"؟‬
You came to kill me!
‫أتيت لتقتلني!‬
You killed the Fortners and the Lieberts…
‫قتلت آل "فورتنر" وآل "ليبرت"‬
and everyone that's ever been kind to us.
‫وكل من عطف علينا.‬
You… killed all of them!
‫قتلتهم جميعًا.‬
You must live!
‫يجب أن تعيش!‬
What?
‫ماذا؟‬
I just said the weather sure is nice today.
‫قلت إن الطقس بديع.‬
Yes, it is.
‫صحيح.‬
Driver.
‫أيها السائق.‬
Yes?
‫نعم؟‬
Can you please drive a little faster?
‫هلّا تقود أسرع.‬
OPERATION ROOM 3
‫"غرفة العمليات ثلاثة"‬
It will be fine. Hang in there.
‫سيكون الأمر على ما يرام. اصمد.‬
Shoot me.
‫أطلقي عليّ النار.‬
Kill him…
‫اقتليه…‬
I'll save you.
‫سأنقذك.‬
Will you shoot me like you did before?
‫هل ستطلقين عليّ النار كما فعلت من قبل؟‬
Yes.
‫نعم.‬
And that'll be the end of this.
‫وسينتهي الأمر بذلك.‬
The end…
‫النهاية…‬
What is the end?
‫ما هي النهاية؟‬
Many, many times I have seen the end.
‫رأيت النهاية مرات عديدة.‬
This is the end!
‫هذه هي النهاية!‬
You will die, and so will I.
‫ستموت وأنا أيضًا.‬
You've seen it?
‫هل رأيت ما حدث؟‬
What have you seen?
‫ماذا رأيت؟‬
What is it you've seen?
‫ما الذي رأيته؟‬
You don't know.
‫أنت لا تعرف.‬
I will tell you…
‫سأخبرك…‬
the truly horrifying story.
‫بالقصة الحقيقية المرعبة.‬
I'm back.
‫عدت.‬